Mecayle Gamba

Entry-level Full Stack Web Developer

Mecayle Gamba

57a Rooihout Street, Bonteheuwel

Cape Town, 8000

067 603 5110 mecayleg@gmail.com https://github.com/MecayleG

I am a young enthusiastic learner who has experience in administration and customer service but would like to broaden my knowledge in terms of technology and programming. I spend most of my free time bettering myself as an individual and trying things I haven't done before. I enjoy doing front-end development but I would really like to continue learning the full stack of web development in more context and learn more languages.

Education

Project Codex / Entry-level full stack web developer

February 2020 - December 2020, Cape Town

Doing a 1 year course to gain skills to become an entry-level full stack web developer.

Frederick Van Zyl Slabbert Institute for Student Leadership Development / Leadership courses completed

February 2016 - October 2016, Stellenbosch

Action Volunteers Africa gave their volunteers the opportunity to do courses in leadership throughout their volunteering journey.

Modderdam High School / Matric

2015 - Bonteheuwel

English Home Language, Afrikaans First Additional Language, History, Business Studies, Life Sciences, Life Orientation, Mathematical Literacy

Hard Skills

- Programming languages (HTML, CSS, Javascript, SQL)
- Templating (Handlebars.js)
- Test Driven Development (Mocha.js, Travis CI)
- Deployment (Git, Heroku)
- Version control
- Server-side programming (using Node and Express.js)
- Command Line

Soft Skills

- Written and verbal communication skills including dealing with customer complaints and data capturing
- Willingness to learn
- Dependable
- Adaptability

Projects

Please refer to my portfolio to see my projects https://mecayleg.github.io/

Work Experience

Customer Service Representative Capita SA, Maitland

September 2019 - December 2019

- Assisting customers with gas and electricity payments
- Capturing customers data to book engineer visits

Administrative Assistant Finlife SA, Claremont

April 2018 - September 2019

- Managing emails from FSP's
- Capturing data from clients certificate of balance onto the FDA system for further evaluation

Administrative Assistant Wastewant Waste Management, Elsies River

July 2017 - February 2018

- Assisting walk in clients with queries about recycling and prices
- Capturing data for attendance, sales and recyclables received
- Assisting operations manager with driver schedules

Achievements

100% attendance recognition from Action Volunteers Africa

Volunteer Experience

2016, Action Volunteers Africa - Volunteer (11 months)

- Tutoring children in numerics and literacy from grades
 1-4
- Completing daily spreadsheets for attendance
- Setting up computers and tablets

References

Andre Vermeulen, CTO, Project Codex

082 726 7879, andre@projectcodex.co

Ghasnad Price, Finlife SA

Admin Manager

076 626 9051, Gprice@finlifesa.co.za

Marnus van der Merwe, Wastewant Waste Management

General Manager 072 731 2775, marnus@richmondimpact.com